In the current war for talent, finding
people is the hardest part. Thanks,
Kurt. I'll take it from here.
You think finding talent is the hard
part? A cute. But getting them in front
of your customers and actually driving
your business forward, that's the real
game. You need to grow your team, but
let's be honest, training new hires
takes time. And
time, that's the one thing you don't
have when customers come knocking. the
speed in which they have joined into our
organization, started adding value. It's
been record-breaking. It enables us to
get consultants that have industry
experience. It also helps taking the
pressure off the existing team. They're
trained on product training,
professional skills, and they have
one-to-one coaching sessions. It would
be much more expensive if we had to do
all of this ourselves. This has to be
part of what you think about and offer
to your team members. You heard it. VC
talent is a full force skilling and
coaching machine and the results they
speak loud and clear just over one year
in and we're proud to share that 233
partner engagements have kicked off of
which 74 are in North America alone 10
weeks from onboarding to billable work
so you keep moving forward no slowdown
93% retention rate because when talent
is trained and coached right they stay
and get
41% of new hires are women. We're not
just filling jobs. We're building a more
diverse, innovative future for Business
Central and its
ecosystem. So, what's it going to be?
Watching from the sidelines or joining
the movement? Come and talk to us.
[Music]
Let's bridge the talent gap together.